A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Civil War Commission, 1952-1966 (bulk 1958-1965)
Library of Virginia
- Series IV.The Wartime Papers of Robert E. Lee, 1959-1961 (photostats and card index: 1832-1870)., Extent: 21 cu. ft. (Box 85-149.)
  - Transcripts, 1833-1865.
    - Chapter Eleven.
      - To General D.H. Hill, 1863 May 30. (Box 99, Folder 33)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 May 30. (Box 99, Folder 34)
      - To Wife, 1863 May 31. (Box 99, Folder 35)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 June 2. (Box 99, Folder 36)
      - To Wife, 1863 June 3. (Box 99, Folder 37)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 June 4. (Box 99, Folder 38)
      - To General A.P. Hill, 1863 June 5. (Box 99, Folder 39)
      - To General I.R. Trimble, 1863 June 7. (Box 99, Folder 40)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 June 7. (Box 99, Folder 41)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 June 8. (Box 99, Folder 42)
      - To Colonel J. Gorgas, 1863 June 8. (Box 99, Folder 43)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1863 June 8. (Box 99, Folder 44)
      - Venable to General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 June 9. (Box 99, Folder 45)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 June 9. (Box 99, Folder 46)
      - To Wife, 1863 June 9. (Box 99, Folder 47)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 June 10. (Box 99, Folder 48)
      - To Fitzhugh Lee, 1863 June 10. (Box 99, Folder 49)
      - To General A.G. Jenkins, 1863 June 10. (Box 99, Folder 50)
      - To General J.D. Imboden, 1863 June 10. (Box 99, Folder 51)
      - To Wife, 1863 June 11. (Box 99, Folder 52)
      - To Fitzhugh's Wife, 1863 June 11. (Box 99, Folder 53)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1863 June 13. (Box 99, Folder 54)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1863 June 13. (Box 99, Folder 55)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 June 15. (Box 99, Folder 56)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 June 15. (Box 99, Folder 57)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 June 15. (Box 99, Folder 58)
      - To General J. Longstreet, 1863 June 15. (Box 99, Folder 59)
      - To General A.P. Hill, 1863 June 16. (Box 99, Folder 60)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1863 June 17. (Box 99, Folder 61)
      - To General James Longstreet, 1863 June 17. (Box 99, Folder 62)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 June 18. (Box 99, Folder 63)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 June 18. (Box 99, Folder 64)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 June 19. (Box 99, Folder 65)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1863 June 19. (Box 99, Folder 66)
      - To General J.D. Imboden, 1863 June 20. (Box 99, Folder 67)
      - To General Samuel Jones, 1863 June 20. (Box 99, Folder 68)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 June 22. (Box 99, Folder 69)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1863 June 22. (Box 99, Folder 70)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1863 June 22. (Box 99, Folder 71)
      - To General James Longstreet, 1863 June 23. (Box 99, Folder 72)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 June 23. (Box 99, Folder 73)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 June 23. (Box 99, Folder 74)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 June 23. (Box 99, Folder 75)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 June 23. (Box 99, Folder 76)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 June 25. (Box 99, Folder 77)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 June 25. (Box 99, Folder 78)
      - General Order, Number 73, 1863 June 27. (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1863 June 28. (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Taylor to General George E. Pickett, 1863 June 29. (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - To Wife, 1863 June 30. (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - To General George E. Pickett, 1863 July 1. (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - To General J.D. Imboden, 1863 July 1. (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - To General J.D. Imboden, 1863 July 4. (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - To Commanding Officer at Winchester, 1863 July 4. (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 4. (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - General Orders, Number 74, 1863 July 4. (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 7. (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - To Wife, 1863 July 7. (Box 100, Folder 12)
      - To General G.E. Pickett, 1863 July 8. (Box 100, Folder 13)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 8. (Box 100, Folder 14)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 July 9. (Box 100, Folder 15)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 10. (Box 100, Folder 16)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 10. (Box 100, Folder 17)
      - Venable to General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 July 11. (Box 100, Folder 18)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 July 12. (Box 100, Folder 19)
      - To Wife, 1863 July 12. (Box 100, Folder 20)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 12. (Box 100, Folder 21)
      - To General Samuel Jones, 1863 July 12. (Box 100, Folder 22)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 July 13. (Box 100, Folder 23)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 14. (Box 100, Folder 24)
      - Circular, 1863 July 14. (Box 100, Folder 25)
      - To Wife, 1863 July 15. (Box 100, Folder 26)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 16. (Box 100, Folder 27)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1863 July 16. (Box 100, Folder 28)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 July 18. (Box 100, Folder 29)
      - To General James Longstreet, 1863 July 19. (Box 100, Folder 30)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 July 20. (Box 100, Folder 31)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1863 July 20. (Box 100, Folder 32)
      - To General J.D. Imboden, 1863 July 21. (Box 100, Folder 33)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 July 21. (Box 100, Folder 34)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 24. (Box 100, Folder 35)
      - To Wife, 1863 July 26. (Box 100, Folder 36)
      - To Miss Margaret Stuart, 1863 July 26. (Box 100, Folder 37)
      - To Mildred Lee, 1863 July 27. (Box 100, Folder 38)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 29. (Box 100, Folder 39)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 31. (Box 100, Folder 40)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 July 31. (Box 100, Folder 41)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 August 1. (Box 100, Folder 42)
      - To Wife, 1863 August 2. (Box 100, Folder 43)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 August 4. (Box 100, Folder 44)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 August 4. (Box 100, Folder 45)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1864 January 20. (Box 100, Folder 46)
    - Chapter Twelve.
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 August 8. (Box 100, Folder 47)
      - To Colonel J. Gorgas, 1863 August 15. (Box 100, Folder 48)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 August 17. (Box 100, Folder 49)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1863 August 18. (Box 100, Folder 50)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 August 22. (Box 100, Folder 51)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 August 24. (Box 100, Folder 52)
      - To General James Longstreet, 1863 August 31. (Box 100, Folder 53)
      - To Wife, 1863 September 4. (Box 100, Folder 54)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 September 6. (Box 100, Folder 55)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 September 9. (Box 100, Folder 56)
      - To Mildred Lee, 1863 September 10. (Box 100, Folder 57)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 September 11. (Box 100, Folder 58)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 September 14. (Box 100, Folder 59)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 September 18. (Box 100, Folder 60)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 September 23. (Box 100, Folder 61)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 September 23. (Box 100, Folder 62)
      - To General A. Elzey, 1863 September 25. (Box 100, Folder 63)
      - To General J. Longstreet, 1863 September 25. (Box 100, Folder 64)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 September 27. (Box 100, Folder 65)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 September 20. (Box 100, Folder 66)
      - To General J.D. Imboden, 1863 October 9. (Box 100, Folder 67)
      - To Seddon, 1863 October 11. (Box 100, Folder 68)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1863 October 13. (Box 100, Folder 69)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 October 17. (Box 100, Folder 70)
      - To General A.R. Lawton, 1863 October 19. (Box 100, Folder 71)
      - To Wife, 1863 October 19. (Box 100, Folder 72)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 October 20. (Box 100, Folder 73)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 October 23. (Box 100, Folder 74)
      - To General Leonidas Polk, 1863 October 26. (Box 100, Folder 75)
      - To Wife, 1863 October 28. (Box 100, Folder 76)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 October 28. (Box 100, Folder 77)
      - To General Samuel Jones, 1863 November 2. (Box 100, Folder 78)
      - To Wife, 1863 November 5. (Box 100, Folder 79)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1863 November 7. (Box 100, Folder 80)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 November 10. (Box 100, Folder 81)
      - To Wife, 1863 November 11. (Box 100, Folder 82)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 November 12. (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - To Agnes, 1863 November 13. (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - To Wife, 1863 November 21. (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 November 26. (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 November 26. (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 November 27. (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 November 28. (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 November 29. (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 November 30. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Chapter Thirteen.
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 December 1. (Box 101, Folder 10)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 December 2. (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 December 2. (Box 101, Folder 12)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 December 2. (Box 101, Folder 13)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 December 3. (Box 101, Folder 14)
      - To Wife, 1863 December 4. (Box 101, Folder 15)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1864 April 27. (Box 101, Folder 16)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 December 3. (Box 101, Folder 17)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 December 7. (Box 101, Folder 18)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 December 9. (Box 101, Folder 19)
      - Taylor to General R.S. Ewell, 1863 December 14. (Box 101, Folder 20)
      - To Mary M.C. Lee, 1863 December 22. (Box 101, Folder 21)
      - To Wife, 1863 December 25. (Box 101, Folder 22)
      - To Wife, 1863 December 27. (Box 101, Folder 23)
      - To Wife, 1863 December 29. (Box 101, Folder 24)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 January 2. (Box 101, Folder 25)
      - To Colonel L.B. Northrop, 1864 January 5. (Box 101, Folder 26)
      - To Wife, 1864 January 10. (Box 101, Folder 27)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1864 January 10. (Box 101, Folder 28)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 January 13. (Box 101, Folder 29)
      - To Wife, 1864 January 15. (Box 101, Folder 30)
      - To General A.R. Lawton, 1864 January 19. (Box 101, Folder 31)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 January 19. (Box 101, Folder 32)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 January 20. (Box 101, Folder 33)
      - To General A.R. Lawton, 1864 January 20. (Box 101, Folder 34)
      - To Colonel John T. Wood, 1864 January 20. (Box 101, Folder 35)
      - To General W. Whiting, 1864 January 20. (Box 101, Folder 36)
      - To General R.F. Hoke, 1864 January 20. (Box 101, Folder 37)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1864 January 20. (Box 101, Folder 38)
      - To Major General Samuel Jones, 1864 January 21. (Box 101, Folder 39)
      - General Orders, Number 7, 1864 January 22. (Box 101, Folder 40)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1864 January 22. (Box 101, Folder 41)
      - To Wife, 1864 January 24. (Box 101, Folder 42)
      - To Brigadier General J.L. Kemper, 1864 January 29. (Box 101, Folder 43)
      - To Brigadier General A.R. Lawton, 1864 January 30. (Box 101, Folder 44)
      - To General Samuel Jones, 1864 February 2. (Box 101, Folder 45)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 February 3. (Box 101, Folder 46)
      - To Wife, 1864 February 6. (Box 101, Folder 47)
      - General Order, Number 15, 1864 February 7. (Box 101, Folder 48)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1864 February 8. (Box 101, Folder 49)
      - To General Arnold Elzey, 1864 February 11. (Box 101, Folder 50)
      - To Wife, 1864 February 14. (Box 101, Folder 51)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1864 February 15. (Box 101, Folder 52)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1864 February 16. (Box 101, Folder 53)
      - To General A. Elzey, 1864 February 18. (Box 101, Folder 54)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 February 18. (Box 101, Folder 55)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1864 February 29. (Box 101, Folder 56)
      - Taylor to General A. Elzey, 1864 February 29. (Box 101, Folder 57)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1864 March 2. (Box 101, Folder 58)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1864 March 2. (Box 101, Folder 59)
      - To General E. Johnson, 1864 March 2. (Box 101, Folder 60)
      - To Major General A. Elzey, 1864 March 3. (Box 101, Folder 61)
      - To J.A. Seddon, 1864 March 6. (Box 101, Folder 62)
      - To Wife, 1864 March 18. (Box 101, Folder 63)
      - To Wife, 1864 March 20. (Box 101, Folder 64)
      - To Wife, 1864 March 24. (Box 101, Folder 65)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 March 25. (Box 101, Folder 66)
      - To General James Longstreet, 1864 March 28. (Box 101, Folder 67)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1864 March 29. (Box 101, Folder 68)
      - To Wife, 1864 March 30. (Box 101, Folder 69)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 March 30. (Box 101, Folder 70)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1864 April 1. (Box 101, Folder 71)
      - To Agnes, 1864 April 3. (Box 101, Folder 72)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 April 5. (Box 101, Folder 73)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1864 April 6. (Box 101, Folder 74)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 April 7. (Box 101, Folder 75)
      - Circular, 1864 April 7. (Box 101, Folder 76)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 April 8. (Box 101, Folder 77)
      - To Wife, 1864 April 9. (Box 101, Folder 78)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1864 April 9. (Box 101, Folder 79)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1864 April 12. (Box 101, Folder 80)
      - To J. Davis, 1864 April 12. (Box 101, Folder 81)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 April 13. (Box 101, Folder 82)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 April 15. (Box 101, Folder 83)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1864 April 16. (Box 101, Folder 84)
      - To General B. Bragg, 1864 April 16. (Box 101, Folder 85)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 April 16. (Box 101, Folder 86)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 April 16. (Box 101, Folder 87)
      - To General J.D. Imboden, 1864 April 18. (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 April 19. (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - To Wife, 1864 April 23. (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 April 29. (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 April 25. (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 April 30. (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1864 April 30. (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 April 30. (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Chapter Fourteen.
      - To General J. Breckinridge, 1864 May 1. (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 May 2. (Box 102, Folder 10)
      - To Wife, 1864 May 2. (Box 102, Folder 11)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 May 4. (Box 102, Folder 12)
      - To Major General J.C. Breckinridge, 1864 May 4. (Box 102, Folder 13)
      - To General J.C. Breckinridge, 1864 May 4. (Box 102, Folder 14)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 4. (Box 102, Folder 15)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 5. (Box 102, Folder 16)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 5. (Box 102, Folder 17)
      - To Secretary of War, 1864 May 5. (Box 102, Folder 18)
      - To Secretary of War, 1864 May 6. (Box 102, Folder 19)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 7. (Box 102, Folder 20)
      - Taylor to General J.E.B. Stuart, 1864 May 7. (Box 102, Folder 21)
      - Taylor to General R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 7. (Box 102, Folder 22)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 8. (Box 102, Folder 23)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 8. (Box 102, Folder 24)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 8. (Box 102, Folder 25)
      - To J.A. Seddon (received), 1864 May 8. (Box 102, Folder 26)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 8. (Box 102, Folder 27)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 10. (Box 102, Folder 28)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 10. (Box 102, Folder 29)
      - To Secretary of War, 1864 May 12. (Box 102, Folder 30)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 12. (Box 102, Folder 31)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 13. (Box 102, Folder 32)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 13. (Box 102, Folder 33)
      - Venable to General R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 14. (Box 102, Folder 34)
      - To General J.Breckinridge, 1864 May 14. (Box 102, Folder 35)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 14. (Box 102, Folder 36)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 15. (Box 102, Folder 37)
      - To Wife, 1864 May 16. (Box 102, Folder 38)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 16. (Box 102, Folder 39)
      - To J.C. Breckinridge, 1864 May 16. (Box 102, Folder 40)
      - To General J. Breckinridge, 1864 May 16. (Box 102, Folder 41)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 17. (Box 102, Folder 42)
      - To General J. Breckinridge, 1864 May 17. (Box 102, Folder 43)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 18. (Box 102, Folder 44)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 18. (Box 102, Folder 45)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 18. (Box 102, Folder 46)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 20. (Box 102, Folder 47)
      - Marshall to General R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 20. (Box 102, Folder 48)
      - Venable to General R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 20. (Box 102, Folder 49)
      - General Orders, Number 44, 1864 May 20. (Box 102, Folder 50)
    - Chapter Fifteen.
      - To J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 21. (Box 102, Folder 51)
      - To R.H. Anderson, 1864 May 21. (Box 102, Folder 52)
      - To Major J.C. Breckinridge, 1864 May 21. (Box 102, Folder 53)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 22. (Box 102, Folder 54)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 22. (Box 102, Folder 55)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 23. (Box 102, Folder 56)
      - To Wife, 1864 May 23. (Box 102, Folder 57)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 23. (Box 102, Folder 58)
      - Taylor to General R.H. Anderson, 1864 May 23. (Box 102, Folder 59)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 May 24. (Box 102, Folder 60)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 24. (Box 102, Folder 61)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 25. (Box 102, Folder 62)
      - Taylor to General R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 26. (Box 102, Folder 63)
      - Taylor to General R.H. Anderson, 1864 May 27. (Box 102, Folder 64)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 27. (Box 102, Folder 65)
      - Taylor to General R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 27. (Box 102, Folder 66)
      - Taylor to General R.H. Anderson, 1864 May 27. (Box 102, Folder 67)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 28. (Box 102, Folder 68)
      - Taylor to General Breckinridge, 1864 May 28. (Box 102, Folder 69)
      - To General J. Breckinridge, 1864 May 28. (Box 102, Folder 70)
      - To J.A. Seddon, 1864 May 28. (Box 102, Folder 71)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 May 29. (Box 102, Folder 72)
      - Special Orders, Number 134, 1864 May 29. (Box 102, Folder 73)
      - To R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 29. (Box 102, Folder 74)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 29. (Box 102, Folder 75)
      - To Wife, 1864 May 29. (Box 102, Folder 76)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 30. (Box 102, Folder 77)
      - To R.H. Anderson, 1864 May 30. (Box 102, Folder 78)
      - To General B. Bragg, 1864 May 30. (Box 102, Folder 79)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 May 30. (Box 102, Folder 80)
      - Taylor to General R.H. Anderson, 1864 May 31. (Box 102, Folder 81)
      - To R.S. Ewell, 1864 May 31. (Box 102, Folder 82)
      - To General A.P. Hill (?), 1864 June (?). (Box 102, Folder 83)
      - To J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 1. (Box 102, Folder 84)
      - To General G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 1. (Box 102, Folder 85)
      - To General G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 1. (Box 102, Folder 86)
      - To General R.S. Ewell, 1864 June 1. (Box 102, Folder 87)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 2. (Box 102, Folder 88)
      - To R.H. Anderson, 1864 June 3. (Box 102, Folder 89)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 3. (Box 102, Folder 90)
      - To Secretary of War, 1864 June 3. (Box 102, Folder 91)
      - To Wife, 1864 June 4. (Box 102, Folder 92)
      - To R.H. Anderson, 1864 June 4. (Box 102, Folder 93)
      - To Secretary of War, 1864 June 4. (Box 102, Folder 94)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 5. (Box 102, Folder 95)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 6. (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - To Wife, 1864 June 7. (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 8. (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - To Wife, 1864 June 8. (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 9. (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 June 9. (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 9. (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - To R.H. Anderson, 1864 June 9. (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 June 9. (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 10. (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 10. (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 11. (Box 103, Folder 12)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 11. (Box 103, Folder 13)
      - To Wife, 1864 June 12. (Box 103, Folder 14)
      - To J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 13. (Box 103, Folder 15)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 14. (Box 103, Folder 16)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 14. (Box 103, Folder 17)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 June 14. (Box 103, Folder 18)
      - To J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 14. (Box 103, Folder 19)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 15. (Box 103, Folder 20)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 June 15. (Box 103, Folder 21)
      - To J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 15. (Box 103, Folder 22)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 15. (Box 103, Folder 23)
      - To General P.G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 16. (Box 103, Folder 24)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 June 16. (Box 103, Folder 25)
      - To General P.G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 16. (Box 103, Folder 26)
      - To General P.G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 16. (Box 103, Folder 27)
      - To General P.G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 16. (Box 103, Folder 28)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 16. (Box 103, Folder 29)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1864 June 17. (Box 103, Folder 30)
      - To General P.G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 17. (Box 103, Folder 31)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 17. (Box 103, Folder 32)
      - To General P.G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 17. (Box 103, Folder 33)
      - To General P.G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 17. (Box 103, Folder 34)
      - To General W.H.F. Lee, 18647 June 17. (Box 103, Folder 35)
      - To General A.P. Hill, 1864 June 17. (Box 103, Folder 36)
      - To General P.G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 17. (Box 103, Folder 37)
      - To General P.G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 17. (Box 103, Folder 38)
      - To General A.P. Hill, 1864 June 17. (Box 103, Folder 39)
      - To General P.G.T. Beauregard, 1864 June 17. (Box 103, Folder 40)
      - To E.H. Gill, 1864 June 18. (Box 103, Folder 41)
      - To General J.A. Early, 1864 June 18. (Box 103, Folder 42)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 18. (Box 103, Folder 43)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 June 18. (Box 103, Folder 44)
      - To General Wade Hampton, 1864 June 18. (Box 103, Folder 45)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1864 June 19. (Box 103, Folder 46)
      - To Wife, 1864 June 19. (Box 103, Folder 47)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1864 June 19. (Box 103, Folder 48)
    - Chapter Sixteen.
      - To J.A. Seddon, 1864 June 22. (Box 103, Folder 49)
      - Taylor to General G.W.C. Lee, 1864 June 22. (Box 103, Folder 50)
      - To General Braxton Bragg, 1864 June 22. (Box 103, Folder 51)
      - To Wife, 1864 June 24. (Box 103, Folder 52)